creme-magazine.com 2013-04-15

# Privacy | Crème Magazine

**Crème Magazine Privacy Policy**

**Crème Magazine respects the personal nature of the information you share on our site and acknowledges the importance of protecting this information. In adopting this privacy policy, our intent is to balance our legitimate business interests in collecting and using your personal information with your reasonable expectations of privacy. The policy may be revised or updated at any time and we encourage you to check back often to ensure that you are familiar with the most recent version and the terms of our policy.**

** ** **1\. You may provide personal information to crème-magazine.com in one of three ways: (1) by sharing your e-mail address and subscribing to email newsletters or requesting site updates, (2) by sharing personal information when you provide tips to our editors, or (3) by sharing personal information when you post comments on our posts or stories. We may also ask for other information at other times but at no time will you be required to share any personal information to gain complete access to our site.**

** ** **2\. In addition to personal information—such as name, street and e-mail addresses, and telephone numbers—we may also collect information that is in no way personally identifiable. This may include the operating system you are working on, the internet browser you are using, the domain name of your internet service provider, and the web sites you visit directly before and after your visit to crème-magazine.com.**

** ** **3\. The e-mail address you provide may be used by crème-magazine.com for any reason, such as contacting you for editorial purposes or to advise you of any changes to our site. We may also from time to time send you messages about our marketing partners’ products.**

** ** **4\. To maintain a site that is free of charge and does not require registration, we display advertisements on our web site. We also use the information you give us to help our advertisers target the audience they want to reach. At no time does any party other than crème-magazine.com have access to your personally identifiable information, and you will never be contacted by any party other than crème-magazine.com. The only exceptions to the foregoing are that we may disclose personally identifiable information (i) in response to legal process, for example, in response to a court order or subpoena, (ii) in response to a law enforcement agency’s request, or where we believe it is necessary to investigate, prevent, or take actions regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of another person, violations of our terms of use, or as otherwise required by law, or (iii) in the event we are acquired by or merged with another company.**

** ** **5\. When you sign up for our updates or receive e-mail messages from crème-magazine.com, you will always be given the chance to opt-out of special offers and site updates. You may change your preferences at any time and will only be contacted in manners consistent with your stated preferences. Non-personally identifiable information (such as stated above) may be shared in aggregate form with our advertisers or marketing partners but your personally identifiable information will never be disclosed to them.**

** ** **6\. The ads appearing on crème-magazine.com are delivered to you by urbanadserve our Web advertising serving partner or an advertisement which our sales staff obtained for the site. Information about your visit to this site, such as number of times you have viewed an ad (but not your name, address, or other personal information), is used to serve ads to you on this site. And, in the course of serving advertisements to this site, third party advertisers may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser.**

** ** **7\. Email newsletters received by subscribers are delivered to you by Constant Contact, our Emarketing solutions provider. Under no circumstances will Constant Contact make any personal information about an individual user available to anyone.**

** ** **8\. We have also contracted with a number of advertising network partners to monitor certain pages of our website and RSS feeds for the purpose of reporting website and RSS traffic, statistics, advertisement ‘click-throughs’, and/or other activities on our website. Where authorized by us, these advertising network partners may use cookies, web beacons, and/or other monitoring technologies to compile anonymous statistics about our website visitors. No personally identifiable information is collected by or transferred to these network partners.**

** ** **9\. Third parties and web sites that have links on our site may also collect or use information about you. The information practices of other companies or people that crème-magazine.com does not employ or manage are not covered by this privacy statement.**

**10\. Any information you disclose voluntarily on our comments pages or in any forums we may develop in the future becomes public information. We cannot control the actions of our site users and advise you to use your discretion in sharing information about yourself on the internet. All information sharing is optional and done so at your own risk. Privacy is a very personal matter and we encourage you to be careful and responsible when disclosing personal information online.**
